{
    "id": "5da37b630f6a4d9d863f0cb01fa236f6",
    "title": "General Vocabulary Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The assassins often ..................... their victims.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "mutilate",
                "castigate",
                "nauseate"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "58876277ae304fb9a38f60c9b2ef8464"
        },
        {
            "question": "The judge ordered him to ………………….. his dog.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "hustle",
                "wrestle",
                "muzzle"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "4550ad1141044e86a3563e33431058b2"
        },
        {
            "question": "There is something ………………….. about his past.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "nauseous",
                "mysterious",
                "nonchalant"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c4d270a634e04529b1840e0c68e3a12d"
        },
        {
            "question": "Her big eyes and ............................ questions made everyone feel protective toward her.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "novel",
                "naive",
                "nauseous"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "1a5dc54987344f9989f9dcb0323d9c5b"
        },
        {
            "question": "The true ......................... of his life was more exciting than fiction.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "definition",
                "narrative",
                "mystery"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "2cb39d32746847a1b95f99154fb02e32"
        },
        {
            "question": "The fare they served would ..................... even a vulture.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "enrage",
                "decapitate",
                "nauseate"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "b9596eee33ab4142b0b8f15ee5930117"
        },
        {
            "question": "He was punished for his ..................... deeds.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "naive",
                "maim",
                "nefarious"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "24c8506522c141a1904a235daba157a2"
        },
        {
            "question": "How can he be so ..................... . in all this trouble?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "nonpartisan",
                "nonchalant",
                "ignominious"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "15e3816bbd474a2cacb71ff101da7623"
        },
        {
            "question": "Tax collection agencies should be ...........................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "nefarious",
                "rational",
                "nonpartisan"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "9e855c1d4bd1408687e48222f8594f65"
        },
        {
            "question": "There is little ....................... in his writing.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "naivety",
                "nebulae",
                "novelty"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "87aeba3d740c4efb8759781f91efa73c"
        }
    ]
}